treyhunner.com 2019-05-23

# Python Morsels -- Privacy Policy

Effective date: **July 1, 2018**

The policy below explains how we collect, share, and retain your personal information and how we communicate with you.

### Data collection

We use common internet technologies, such as cookies and web server logs to collect basic usage information. We collect this information from everyone, whether you have an account or not.

When you create a Python Morsels account, you provide your email address, password, and optionally other information. We do not collect credit card numbers or payment information, but our third-party payment processor does.

We process all personal information you provide to us on the basis of consent. The remainder of the processing of personal information we perform is necessary for our legitimate interests, for example logs of IP addresses for website accesses may be maintained for security purposes.

We use your personal information for internal purposes, such as for customer service. If we would like to use your personal information for another purpose, we will ask your permission first.

### Data sharing

We will not share your personal information with third parties or visitors to the Python Morsels website unless you give us permission to do so. For example, if you provide us with a testimonial we will ask for your permission to list the testimonial on our website.

We do share personal information with a limited number of third party vendors who process it on our behalf to provide or improve our service.

### Data retention

Generally, we will retain your personal information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services.

We don't automatically delete inactive user accounts, so we will retain your account information indefinitely unless you contact us to delete your account.

If you would like to request erasure of data we process on the basis of consent or object to our processing of personal information, please [contact us](mailto:help@pythonmorsels.com).

### Communication

We will use your email address to communicate with you. For example, if you contact us with a support request, we will respond to you via email.

Please note that you can not opt out of receiving important communications from us, such as support emails, but you can configure your email settings on your account settings page.
